Guide to the Union for Radical Political Economics and Review of radical political economics records, 1961-2013.
Union for Radical Political Economics and Review of radical political economics records, 1961-2013
- Series IV. URPE Records 1969-1986
  - URPE miscellany, 1971-1972 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - URPE miscellany, 1972-1973 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - URPE miscellany, 1973-1974 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - URPE miscellany, 1973-1974 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - URPE, 1973-1974 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - URPE, 1974-1975 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - URPE, 1974-1975 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - URPE, 1974-1975 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Occ Papers: Cozy, 1969 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Food Packet (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Correspondence to and from Michael Zweig, 1961-1969 (Box 41, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence to and from Michael Zweig, 1970-1975 (Box 41, Folder 2)
  - Graduate student memos, clippings, proposals, 1966 (Box 41, Folder 3)
  - URPE founding documents, 1968 (Box 41, Folder 4)
  - URPE bylaws, memos and correspondence, 1969-1970 (Box 41, Folder 5)
  - Course material, 1970-1971 (Box 41, Folder 6)
  - Women; work project, 1970 (Box 41, Folder 7)
    Includes brochures and papers
  - Dictatorship of the Bourgeoisie, 1972 (Box 41, Folder 8)
    Proposed collection of readings
  - URPE material, 1970-1972 (Box 41, Folder 9)
    Includes correspondence, memos, clippings, publications, resolutions
  - URPE material, 1970-1972 (Box 41, Folder 9)
    Includes correspondence, memos, clippings, publciations, reolutions
  - URPE New York region, 1972-1974 (Box 41, Folder 10)
  - URPE material, 1973 (Box 41, Folder 11)
  - URPE PEAC and Food, 1972-1974 (Box 41, Folder 12)
    Includes memos, clippings, publciations, reports
  - URPE material, 1974 (Box 41, Folder 13)
  - Ad Hoc Committee for Teach-ins, 1974 (Box 41, Folder 14)
  - URPE material, 1975-1977 (Box 41, Folder 15)
  - URPE New York region, 1975-1976 (Box 41, Folder 16)
    Includes correspondence, memos, clippings, proposals, publications
  - URPE material, 1981-1986 (Box 41, Folder 17)
- Series V. Publications
  (note: Issues of the Review of Radical and Political Economics, Vol. I, no. 1 - Vol. VI - no. 1, and Reprint no. 1, "The Basic Economics of the Urban and Racial Crisis." by Daniel R. Tusfeld have been transferred to Gifts and Exchange. See the accessions folder for a list.)
  - Sub-series A: URPE Newsletter
    - Vol. 1, no. 1-4; Vol. 2, no. 1-4; -Vol. 3, no. 1-5, 1969-1971 (Box 6, Folder 14)
    - Vol. 4, no. 1-4; Vol. 5, no. 1-6, 1972-1973 (Box 6, Folder 15)
    - Vol. 6, no. 1-6; Vol. 7, no. 1-6, 1974-1975 (Box 6, Folder 16)
    - Vol. 8, no. 1-6; Vol. 9, no. 1-2, 4-6, 1976-1977 (Box 6, Folder 17)
    - Vol. 10, no. 1-6; Vol. 11, no. 1-6, 1978-1979 (Box 6, Folder 18)
    - Vol. 12, no. 1-6; Vol. 13, no. 1-4, 6, 1980-1981 (Box 6, Folder 19)
    - Vol. 14, no. 1-6; Vol. 15, no. 1-6; Vol. 16, no. 1-4; Vol. 17, no. 1-4; Vol. 18 no. 1-3; Vol. 19, no. 2-4; Vol. 20, no. 1-4, 1982-1989 (Box 6, Folder 20)
    - Vol. 21, no. 1-6; Vol. 22, no. 2-3; Vol. 23, no. 1-3; Vol. 24, no. 4; Vol. 25 no. 1-4; Vol. 26, no. 1-2; Vol. 27, no. 1-4, 1989-1996 (Box 6, Folder 21)
    - Vol. 28, no. 1-4; Vol. 29, no. 1-4; Vol. 30, no. 1-4; Vol. 31, no. 1-4; Vol. 32 no. 1-4; Vol. 33, no. 1-4; Vol. 34, no. 1-4, 1996-2003 (Box 6, Folder 22)
    - Vol.1, no. 2., 1969 (Box 4, Folder 19)
    - URPE Newsletter, 1999-2005 (Box 13, Folder 98)
    - URPE Newsletter, 2005-2010 (Box 13, Folder 99)
    - Philadelphia "Reality Tour", 2004-2005 (Box 6, Folder 27)
    - Special URPE issue honoring David Gordon, 1996-1997 (Box 6, Folder 28)
    - Urban Special Issue honoring Matt Edel, 1996-1997 (Box 6, Folder 29)
  - Sub-series B: Conference Papers.
    - 1968-12 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Sub-series C: Reprints
    - Tusfeld, Daniel R. "Fascist Democracy in the United States." Reprint no. 2 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Sub-series D: Occasional Papers
    - No 1 and 2 Light, Donald. "Income Distribution: the First Stage in the Consideration of Poverty." and Dowd, Douglas E. "The Economic History of the United States in the Twentieth Century." (Box 4, Folder 22)
    - No. 4 Dowd, Douglas F. "The State, Power and the Industrial Revolution, 1750-1914" (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Sub-series E: Pamphlet Collective.
    - "Radical Perspectives on the Economic Crisis of Monopoly Capitalism ..." Published by URPE Political Education and Action Project Pamphlet Collective (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Sub-series F: Other Publications.
    - Why Do We Spend So Much Money? 3rd Edition, 1977 (Box 7, Folder 30)
    - Three Women's Work Project Booklets: Separated & Unequal: Discrimination Against Women Workers After World War II (The U.A.W. 1944-1954), Women Organizing the Office, Women In Health, ca. 1976-1978 (Box 7, Folder 31)
    - A Concept by George W. Brailsford, 1995 (Box 7, Folder 32)
    - The Campaign to Reward Work: Arguments for a $6.25 Missouri Minimum Wage, 1996 (Box 7, Folder 33)
    - Step by Step, 1965; Fayette County Project (Box 7, Folder 34)
    - Year One, number 1, October 1969 (Box 7, Folder 35)
    - Africa, first issue, February 1969 (Box 7, Folder 36)
    - Howard Wachtel publications, no date (Box 41, Folder 18)
    - Radical education project publications, 1961-1967 (Box 41, Folder 19)
    - Radicals in the Professions Newsletters, 1967-11-1969-03 (Box 41, Folder 20)
    - Radical education project publications, 1961-1967 (Box 41, Folder 19)
    - Radical education project publications, 1961-1967 (Box 41, Folder 20)
    - Various memos and publications, 1968 (Box 41, Folder 21)
    - Publication - Something Else, 1969-1971 (Box 41, Folder 22)
    - Ripsaw - published by the graduate student union of Columbia University, 1969 (Box 41, Folder 23)
    - NYCURPE newsfliers, 1974 (Box 41, Folder 24)
    - URPE/Political education and action project - The Energy Crisis: A Matter of Profits, 1974 (Box 41, Folder 25)
    - U.S. Capitalism in Crisis, 1978 (Box 41, Folder 26)
- Series VI. The Review of Radical Political Economics (RRPE)
  - RRPE Volume 1, Number 1, May 1969 (Box 7, Folder 1)
    Photocopy
  - RRPE Special issue, May 1969 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - RRPE Volume 2, Number 1, Spring 1970 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - RRPE Volume 2, Number 2, Summer 1970 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - RRPE Volume 2, Number 3: Special Issue: The War and Its Impact on the Economy, 1970-08 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - RRPE Volume 2, Number 4, Fall 1970 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - RRPE Volume 3, Number 1: Case Studies in Imperialism and Underdevelopment, Spring 1971 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - RRPE Volume 3, Number 2: Special Issue On Radical Paradigms in Economics, 1971-07 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - RRPE Volume 3, Number 3: Capitalism, Inequality, and Poverty, Summer 1971 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - RRPE Volume 3, Number 4, Fall/Winter 1971 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - RRPE Volume 4, Number 1: Dependency and Foreign Domination in the Third World, Winter 1972 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - RRPE Volume 4, Number 2, Summer 1972 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - RRPE Volume 4, Number 3: The Political Economy of Women, 1972-07 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - RRPE Volume 4, Number 4: Special Issue On the New Economic Policy: The New Economics and the Contradictions of Keynesianism, 1972-08 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - RRPE Volume 4, Number 5, Fall 1972 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - RRPE Volume 5, Number 1: Capitalism and World Economic Integration: Perspectives on Modern Imperialism, Spring 1973 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - RRPE Volume 5, Number 3: Chile and Copper, Prospects for U.S. Fascism, Obsolescence of Growth, Politics and Radical Economists, Fall 1973 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - RRPE Volume 6, Number 1: Some Contradictions of Advanced Capitalism, Spring 1974 (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - RRPE Volume 6, Number 3, Fall 1974 (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - RRPE Volume 6, Number 4, Winter 1975 (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - RRPE Volume 7, Number 4, Winter 1975 (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - RRPE Volume 8, Number 3, Fall 1976 (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - RRPE Volume 9, Number 2, Summer 1977 (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - RRPE Volume 10, Number 4, Winter 1978 (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - RRPE Volume 11, Number 2, Summer 1979 (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - RRPE Volume 11, Number 4, Winter 1979 (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - RRPE Volume 12, Number 3, Fall 1980 (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - RRPE Volume 15, Number 2: Economic Depression - Past & Present, The IMF-A Critique, Neo-Ricardians vs. Fundamentalists, Summer 1983 (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - RRPE Volume 20, Numbers 2 & 3: Papers of the URPE at the ASSA Meetings, New York City, December 28-30, 1988, Summer/Fall 1988 (Box 7, Folder 29)
- Series VII. Summer Conference Papers
  - Summer Conference Registrations, 1973 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Summer Conference, 1974 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Summer Conference, 1974 (Box 42, Folder 3)
  - Summer Conference, 1974 (Box 42, Folder 4)
  - Summer Conference Business Meetings, 1975 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Summer Conference, 1976 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Summer Conference, 1977 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Summer Conference, 1979 (Box 42, Folder 9)
  - Summer Conference, 1978 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Summer Conference Registrations and Finances, 1978 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Summer Conference, 1979 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Summer Conference Notebook (I), 1977-1979 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Summer Conference Notebook (2), 1977-1979 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Summer Conference, 1980 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Summer Conference Business Meeting, 1980 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Summer Conference, 1981 (Box 42, Folder 11)
  - Summer Conference, 1981 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Summer Conference Planning, 1981 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Summer Conference Business Meeting, 1981 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Summer Conference Finances, 1981 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Summer Conference Program and Business Meeting, 1982 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Summer Conference Finances, 1982 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Summer Conference Miscellany, 1982 (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Summer Conference Registration Questionnaire, 1982 (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - Summer Conference Registrations, 1983 (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - Summer Conference Finances, 1983 (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - Summer Conference Business Meetings, 1983 (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - Summer Conference Planning, 1983 (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - Summer Conference, 1984 (Box 8, Folder 25)
  - Summer Conference Information, 1984 (Box 8, Folder 26)
  - Summer Conference Registrations, 1984 (Box 8, Folder 27)
  - Summer Conference Finances, 1984 (Box 8, Folder 28)
  - Summer Conference, 1985 (Box 8, Folder 29)
  - Summer Conference Registrations, 1985 (Box 8, Folder 30)
  - Summer Conference Miscellany, 1985 (Box 8, Folder 31)
  - Summer Conference, 1986 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Summer Conference Registrations (I), 1986 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Summer Conference Registrations (II), 1986 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Summer Conference Finances, 1986 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Summer Conference Correspondence, 1986 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Summer Conference Publicity, 1986 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Summer Conference, 1987 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Summer Conference Registrations, 1987 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Summer Conference Papers, 1987-1988 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Summer Conference Registrations, 1988 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Summer Conference Correspondence, 1988 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Summer Conference Publicity, 1988 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Summer Conference, 1989 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Summer Conference Registrations, 1989 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Summer Conference, 1990 (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - Summer Conference Registrations, 1990 (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - Summer Conference, 1991 (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - Summer Conference Registrations, 1991 (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - Summer Conference, 1992 (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - Summer Conference, 1993 (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - Summer Conference, 1993 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Summer Conference Registrations, 1993 (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - Summer Conference Registrations, 1994 (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - Summer Conference, 1994 (Box 9, Folder 23)
  - Summer Conference, 2001 (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - Summer Conference, 2002 (Box 6, Folder 26)
- Series VIII. Other Conferences
  - Conference papers: Economics Movement, 1966-1968 (Box 6, Folder 2-6)
  - Conference on Radicals in the Professions, 1967 (Box 41, Folder 27)
  - Vocations for Radicals Conference, 1968-03-08-1968-03-10 (Box 41, Folder 28)
  - Radical Economics Conference in Ann Arbor, 1968-09 (Box 42, Folder 1)
  - Discussion papers, 1968 (Box 42, Folder 2)
  - URPE conference, 1968-12, 1975-12 (Box 42, Folder 5)
  - Various conferences, 1976 (Box 42, Folder 6)
  - Mailing lists for international conference, 1976 (Box 42, Folder 7)
  - URPE conferences, 1977 (Box 42, Folder 8)
  - Conference on the nature of the Soviet Union and its role in the world today, 1979-03 (Box 42, Folder 10)
  - Women's Caucus, 1975-1989 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Women's Work Project, 1976-1979 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - American Economic Association, 1976-1977 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - ASSA Conference Programs, 1972-1982 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Miscellaneous ASSA Correspondence, 1973 (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - ASSA Conference, 1974 (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - ASSA Conference Program Schedules, 1975 (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - ASSA Conference Housing, Transportation, Miscellany, 1975 (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - ASSA Conference, Speaker Correspondence, 1975 (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - ASSA Conference, ASSA Correspondence, 1975 (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - ASSA Conference, Other Correspondence, 1975 (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - ASSA Conference, 1976 (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - Economic Census, 1977 (Box 10, Folder 22)
  - ASSA Equal Rights Amendment Boycott, 1979 (Box 10, Folder 23)
  - Equal Rights Amendment at ASSA Conference, 1979 (Box 10, Folder 24)
  - ASSA Conference, 1979 (Box 10, Folder 25)
  - Political Economy of the Third World Conference, 1979 (Box 10, Folder 26)
  - Journalism Conference, 1981 (Box 10, Folder 27)
  - ASSA Conference, 1981 (Box 10, Folder 28)
  - Energy Conference, 1981 (Box 10, Folder 29)
  - Inflation Conference, 1982 (Box 10, Folder 30)
  - ASSA Conference, 1982 (Box 10, Folder 31)
  - ASSA Conference Registrations, 1983 (Box 10, Folder 32)
  - ASSA Conference, 1984 (Box 10, Folder 33)
  - ASSA Conference, 1985 (Box 10, Folder 34)
  - High-Tech Caucus, 1985 (Box 10, Folder 35)
  - ASSA Conference, 1986 (Box 10, Folder 36)
  - Socialist Scholars Conference, 1986 (Box 10, Folder 37)
  - Socialist Scholars Conference, 1987 (Box 10, Folder 38)
  - Eastern Economic Association Conference, 1987 (Box 10, Folder 39)
  - ASSA Conference, 1987 (Box 10, Folder 40)
  - ASSA Conference, 1988 (Box 10, Folder 41)
  - Other Conferences, 1986-1994 (Box 10, Folder 42)
  - ASSA Conference, 1993 (Box 6, Folder 1)
- Series IX. URPE Steering Committee
  - BAG, 1977 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - BAG, 1978 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - BAG, 1979 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - BAG, 1980 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - BAG, 1981 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - BAG, 1982 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Steering Committee, 1970 (Box 42, Folder 12)
  - Steering Committee, 1973 (Box 42, Folder 13)
  - Steering Committee, 1974 (Box 42, Folder 14)
  - Steering Committee, 1975 (Box 42, Folder 15)
  - Steering Committee, 1974-1975 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Steering Committee Miscellany (I), 1977-1988 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Steering Committee Miscellany (II), 1977-1988 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Steering Committee Miscellany, 1979-1984 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Steering Committee, 1977-1978 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Steering Committee, 1978-1979 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Steering Committee, 1979-1980 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Steering Committee, 1980-1981 (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Steering Committee, 1981-1982 (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Steering Committee, 1983-1984 (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - Steering Committee, 1984-1986 (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - Steering Committee, 1986-1987 (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - Steering Committee, 1987-1988 (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - Steering Committee, 1988-1989 (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - Steering Committee, 1989-1990 (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - Steering Committee, 1990 (Box 11, Folder 22)
  - Steering Committee Report, 1990-1991 (Box 11, Folder 23)
  - Steering Committee, 1991 (Box 11, Folder 24)
  - Steering Committee Report on RRPE Publishing, 1991 (Box 11, Folder 25)
  - Steering Committee, 1992 (Box 11, Folder 26)
  - Steering Committee, 1992-1993 (Box 11, Folder 27)
  - Steering Committee, 1993-1994 (Box 11, Folder 28)
  - Steering Committee, 2001 (Box 6, Folder 33)
  - Steering Committee, 2002 (Box 6, Folder 34)
  - Steering Committee, 2003 (Box 6, Folder 35)
- Series X. URPE Records and Miscellany
  - URPE material, 1976 (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - URPE material, 1979 (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - Early Correspondence and By-Laws, 1969-1973 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - URPE Financial Statements and Annual Reports, 1971-1976 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Food Packet, 1973 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - URPE Scrapbook and Newspaper Articles, 1970-1987 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Friedman Protest, 1976 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Economics Education Project, 1977-1980 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Fundraising Letters, 1977-1984 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Library Subscription Drive, 1985 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Publicity, Newspaper Articles, 1986-1988 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Undergraduate Essay Content (I), 1990 (Box 10, Folder 43)
  - Undergraduate Essay Content (II), 1990 (Box 10, Folder 44)
  - Undergraduate Essay Content (III), 1990 (Box 10, Folder 45)
  - Undergraduate Essay Content, 1991 (Box 10, Folder 46)
  - Budget and Finance Information, 1976-1986 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Publisher Correspondence, 1990-1992 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Publisher Correspondence, 1992-1993 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Publisher Correspondence, 1993-1994 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Freedom of Information Act (FOIA), 1981-1985 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - FBI Freedom of Information Correspondence, 1982-1984 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - FBI Freedom of Information Court Papers, ca. 1982 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - China Trip, 1979 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Reading Lists in Radical Social Science Production Correspondence, 1981-1982 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Crisis in the Public Sector Publication Production, 1980 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Stock Market News Articles, 1987 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - RRPE Editorial Board, 1971-1978 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - RRPE Editorial Board, 1981-1982 (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - RRPE Editorial Board Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1978-1987 (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - RRPE Editorial Board Miscellaenous Correspondence, 1989-1990 (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - Blackwell Publishers Correspondence, 1990-1993 (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - Blackwell Publishers Correspondence, 1994-1996 (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - URPE Newsletter Production Volume 20, 1989-1990 (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - URPE Newsletter Production Volume 22, 1991 (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - Luis Prado Correspondence, 1981-1983 (Box 12, Folder 20)
  - Capp Street Foundation Grants, 1981-1983 (Box 12, Folder 21)
  - Tax Exempt Status Papers, 1978-1981 (Box 12, Folder 22)
  - Imperiled Economy Publicatoin Production, 1987 (Box 12, Folder 23)
  - URPE Newsletter Artwork and Comics (Box 12, Folder 24)
  - Workers Education Local 189, 1980-1982 (Box 12, Folder 25)
  - URPE Membership Handbook (Box 12, Folder 26)
  - URPE Certificate of Incorporation and By-Laws (Box 12, Folder 27)
  - Copyright Requests and Correspondence, 1970-1988 (Box 12, Folder 28)
  - Copyright Registrations, 1971-1989 (Box 12, Folder 29)
  - Copyright Registrations, 1990-1993 (Box 12, Folder 30)
  - Dissolution of URPE in California, 1996-1997 (Box 12, Folder 31)
  - URPE Mailing List, 1991 (Box 12, Folder 32)
  - URPE National Office Policies, Procedures (Box 12, Folder 33)
  - Reading Lists, 1979 (Box 12, Folder 34)
  - Reading Lists Correspondence, 1977-1988 (Box 12, Folder 35)
  - Committee on Political Discrimination, 1975-1979 (Box 12, Folder 36)
  - Michigan Police Records, 1989 (Box 12, Folder 37)
  - Political Education and Action (PEA) Project, 1973-1974 (Box 12, Folder 38)
  - URPE Contributions, 1988-1990 (Box 12, Folder 39)
  - "Radical Economics at UCR Reclaiming Socialism" newspaper article from The Press-Enterprise, 1991-10-14 (Box 12, Folder 40)
  - Finance Committee Proposal and Reports, 1979-1981 (Box 12, Folder 41)
  - URPE Posters (Box 12, Folder 42)
  - Copy Rights, 1979-2008 (Box 13, Folder 1-48)
  - Papers from Washington Meeting, 1995 (Box 13, Folder 49-79)
  - Editorial Board Meetings, 1996-2004 (Box 13, Folder 80)
  - Editorial Board Meetings, 2001-2007 (Box 13, Folder 81)
  - Laibman Lecture, 2005 (Box 13, Folder 82)
  - Darity Lecture, 2008 (Box 13, Folder 83)
  - Epstein Lecture, 2009 (Box 13, Folder 84)
  - History of Radical Economics, 2003-2004 (Box 13, Folder 85)
  - Pedagogy, 2007-2009 (Box 13, Folder 86)
  - Consumption, 2003-2006 (Box 13, Folder 87)
  - Globalization, 2002-2004 (Box 13, Folder 88)
  - Political Economy of Food, 2004-2007 (Box 13, Folder 89)
  - Economic Democracy, 2007-2011 (Box 13, Folder 90)
  - Special Issue on Water, 2010 (Box 13, Folder 91)
  - Special Issue on China, 2010 (Box 13, Folder 92)
  - Special Issue on Financialization, 2009 (Box 13, Folder 93)
  - Correspondence, 1999-2003 (Box 13, Folder 94)
  - Steering Committee, 1998-2004 (Box 13, Folder 95)
  - ASSA Correspondence, 1990-2006 (Box 13, Folder 96)
  - URPE Special Issues Vol. 38-42 (Box 13, Folder 100)
  - Not-for-Profit Status, 1970-1977 (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - URPE By-Laws (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - Loans, 1989-1990 (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - Tax Records, 1990-1991 (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - UC Riverside Work-Study Program, 1991 (Box 14, Folder 19)
  - Meeting agendas, 1990-2000 (Box 6, Folder 30)
  - Editorial Board Members, 1992-2001 (Box 6, Folder 31)
  - Editorial Board expenses, 2000-2003 (Box 6, Folder 32)
  - Manuscript Design ideas (Box 5, Folder 96)
  - Article topic: Art, 2002 (Box 5, Folder 97)
  - Article topic: Value Theory, 1999 (Box 5, Folder 98)
  - Article topic: Iran, 2000-2001 (Box 5, Folder 99)
  - National Office Review, 2002-2003 (Box 5, Folder 100)
  - Insurance URPE, 1999-2001 (Box 5, Folder 101)
  - Editorial Board meeting minutes, 2002-2003 (Box 5, Folder 102)
  - Budgets, 1998-2003 (Box 5, Folder 103)
  - URPE office in Amherst, 2002-2003 (Box 5, Folder 104)
  - Survey concerning annual conference (Box 5, Folder 105)
  - URPE Sustainer contributions, 2002 (Box 5, Folder 106)
  - E-mails - various topics, 2002-2003 (Box 5, Folder 107)
  - Sage Publications proposal to publish RRPE, 2002 (Box 5, Folder 108)
  - Applications for Managing Editor Position, 2014 (Box 36, Folder 56)
  - Elections, 2010-2015 (Box 40, Folder 74)
  - Editorial Board Meetings, 2004-2010 (Box 40, Folder 75)
  - Editorial Board Meetings, 2011-2015 (Box 40, Folder 76)
  - Annual Reports, 2010-2012 (Box 40, Folder 77)
  - URPE Newsletter, 2011-2014 (Box 40, Folder 78)
  - URPE Tax and By Laws, 2008-2012 (Box 40, Folder 79)
  - URPE Steering Committee, 2006-2014 (Box 40, Folder 80)